<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:magento:module:MageSuite_Changelog:etc/changelog.xsd">
    <module id="Theme_Creativeshop" name="Theme_Creativeshop">
        <changelog>
            <tag version="17.0.0" date="2022-01-28">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Next generation sliders, teasers and product tiles</overview>
                    <description>
                        This release introduces a refactor for slider-based components,
                        like image-teasers and products-carousels, as well as the new structure
                        and architecture for product tile. It gets rid of a Swiper library,
                        replacing JS-based slider with modern CSS solutions and simplyfing product-tile,
                        thanks to CSS Grid possibilities, which gives us more flexibility of styling tile per project,
                        without element's duplication, overwriting or complex layout changes.
                        Note that these changes drop some of the functionalities of slider elements
                        and change strucutures of product tiles and teasers, so they need much attention during the udpate.
                        Chages are spread across many MageSuite modules.

                        More details can be found in:
                        https://creativestyle.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/CSHOP/pages/2135359509/Next+generation+Teaser+Slider+and+Product+Tile
                    </description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.1.0" date="2022-03-21">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>In-place Video Teasers and Consent Management component</overview>
                    <description>
                        Introduces support for new Content Constructor possibilities - placing a Video inside of teaser-based components
                        https://creativestyle.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/MGS/pages/2017525775/2.16.+Video+Teasers
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>PERFORMANCE</type>
                    <overview>Breakpoint utility refactor and breakpoint change event introduced</overview>
                    <description>New "breakpointChange" event on document has been implemented, that can be referenced instead of widndow resize listeners taht affect performance</description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.2.0" date="2022-04-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>PERFORMANCE</type>
                    <overview>Serve google fonts locally</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.3.0" date="2022-04-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improved scroll snap for iOS</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to add autorotate to sliders on mobile</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Brand carousel configuration moved to view.xml, for more flexible customization</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.4.0" date="2022-04-19">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add missing deafult scheme to navigation teaser config</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improve behaviour of search field and offcanvas navigation on mobile</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.5.0" date="2022-05-05">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to set custom settings for products carousel in offcanvas minicart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Resolve JS issues with reviews on PDP component</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add animating wishlist badge for support of AJAX "Add to wishlist"</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improve slider autorotation - clear autorotate interval before starting new one</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>SECURITY</type>
                    <overview>Resolve security vulnerabilities in templates</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.6.0" date="2022-06-20">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to set custom settings for products carousel in offcanvas minicart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>DEFAULT</type>
                    <overview>Remove support for carousel with the list view</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove Magento Page Builder leftovers on cateory pages entirely</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add support for autorotation in slider - for mobile devices as an option</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Support for MageSuite Instant Purchase feature</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.6.1" date="2022-07-01">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Eager load posibility for Hero Teaser</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fixed reviews pagination/load more button when user click on review link in buybox</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fixed sorting, that switched back to default after jumping pages with paginaton</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.0" date="2022-07-11">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Support for Magento 2.4.4</overview>
                    <description>Templates have been aligned with Magento core</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Swatches refactor</overview>
                    <description>Swatches logic was refactored in order to improve performance and fix issues with displaying price modificators. New changes allow projects to easily apply customizations.</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add optional styles for file-attachments module</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add styles for add-to-homescreen guide and refactor notification-panel styles</overview>
                    <description>
                        Styles and icons for new component - a2hs-guide was added. It replaced pwa-notification comppnent.
                        Push-notifications component was renamed into notification-panel.
                        --shipping modifier for notification-panel was replaced with more neutral --slim
                        Styles for a2hs-guide and notifications-panel are commented - they are optional now.
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add additional, universal class for buybox add to wishlist icon</overview>
                    <description>
                        In order to make theme compatible with magesuite-wishlist module
                        add a class to wishlist icon to allowa ajax add to wishlist badge animation
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add proper image width for autocomplete image</overview>
                    <description>
                        New image optimization functionality by default does not add additional white space in order to fit defiened image size.
                        In order to makeimage optimization faster it is recommended to define real sizes (aspect ratio) for product images.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4641</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add data-product-id to buybox wishlist icon</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add data-product-id to buybox wishlist icon in order to add selected class if given product is already added to the wishlist
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1422</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix pwa-a2hs-guide styles</overview>
                    <description>
                        Fix for: Buttons are overlapping when I added a static block
                        Fix for: Missing arrow when a static block is added (mobile)
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix translation and remove leftover custom-modal styles</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>PDP Gallery: Improved Cumulative Layout Shift</overview>
                    <description>
                        Removed styles that affect browser flow in keeping a space for image that is still loading.
                        Cleaned up webp-related code, as not supported anymore.
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>improve SEO: Add custom tag support for product details headlines, fix footer and minicart headlines, add proper styles</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>fix checkout agreements visiblity for orders with only payment step (virtual products and gift cards)</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix style of disabled swatches displayed on product tile when Back-In-Stock feature is active</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add missing styles for related products carousels in cart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Unify "My Addresses" string to get the correct breadcrumbs translation in user area</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix amazon divider for multiple lines</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3273</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix button 'show more', which not hide after load last items</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4372</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>DEFAULT</type>
                    <overview>Bigger cleanup of the whole theme-creativeshop components, entries and folder structure</overview>
                    <description>Changes are described in breaking_changes_v18 documentation</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Implement additional function for getting video configuration so child projects can extend it</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3244</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix support for removing item from cart by setting Qty lesser than min value</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-2745</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add support for Elasticsuite Instant Search</overview>
                    <description>
                        Commit introduces changes to instant search form.mini.phtml template and provides optional components to be used
                        in projects with Elasticsuite Premium feature - Instant Search
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4665</ticket_id>
                    <doc_reference>elasticsearch_instant_search_integration.md</doc_reference>
                </entry>
            </tag>
        </changelog>
    </module>
</config>
