<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:magento:module:MageSuite_Changelog:etc/changelog.xsd">
    <module id="Theme_Creativeshop" name="Theme_Creativeshop">
        <changelog>
            <tag version="17.0.0" date="2022-01-28">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Next generation sliders, teasers and product tiles</overview>
                    <description>
                        This release introduces a refactor for slider-based components,
                        like image-teasers and products-carousels, as well as the new structure
                        and architecture for product tile. It gets rid of a Swiper library,
                        replacing JS-based slider with modern CSS solutions and simplyfing product-tile,
                        thanks to CSS Grid possibilities, which gives us more flexibility of styling tile per project,
                        without element's duplication, overwriting or complex layout changes.
                        Note that these changes drop some of the functionalities of slider elements
                        and change strucutures of product tiles and teasers, so they need much attention during the udpate.
                        Chages are spread across many MageSuite modules.

                        More details can be found in:
                        https://creativestyle.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/CSHOP/pages/2135359509/Next+generation+Teaser+Slider+and+Product+Tile
                    </description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.1.0" date="2022-03-21">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>In-place Video Teasers and Consent Management component</overview>
                    <description>
                        Introduces support for new Content Constructor possibilities - placing a Video inside of teaser-based components
                        https://creativestyle.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/MGS/pages/2017525775/2.16.+Video+Teasers
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>PERFORMANCE</type>
                    <overview>Breakpoint utility refactor and breakpoint change event introduced</overview>
                    <description>New "breakpointChange" event on document has been implemented, that can be referenced instead of widndow resize listeners taht affect performance</description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.2.0" date="2022-04-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>PERFORMANCE</type>
                    <overview>Serve google fonts locally</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.3.0" date="2022-04-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improved scroll snap for iOS</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to add autorotate to sliders on mobile</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Brand carousel configuration moved to view.xml, for more flexible customization</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.4.0" date="2022-04-19">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add missing deafult scheme to navigation teaser config</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improve behaviour of search field and offcanvas navigation on mobile</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.5.0" date="2022-05-05">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to set custom settings for products carousel in offcanvas minicart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Resolve JS issues with reviews on PDP component</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add animating wishlist badge for support of AJAX "Add to wishlist"</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Improve slider autorotation - clear autorotate interval before starting new one</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>SECURITY</type>
                    <overview>Resolve security vulnerabilities in templates</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.6.0" date="2022-06-20">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Possibility to set custom settings for products carousel in offcanvas minicart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>DEFAULT</type>
                    <overview>Remove support for carousel with the list view</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove Magento Page Builder leftovers on cateory pages entirely</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add support for autorotation in slider - for mobile devices as an option</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Support for MageSuite Instant Purchase feature</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="17.6.1" date="2022-07-01">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Eager load posibility for Hero Teaser</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fixed reviews pagination/load more button when user click on review link in buybox</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fixed sorting, that switched back to default after jumping pages with paginaton</overview>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.0" date="2022-12-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Support for Magento 2.4.4</overview>
                    <description>Templates have been aligned with Magento core</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Swatches refactor</overview>
                    <description>Swatches logic was refactored in order to improve performance and fix issues with displaying price modificators. New changes allow projects to easily apply customizations.</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add optional styles for file-attachments module</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add styles for add-to-homescreen guide and refactor notification-panel styles</overview>
                    <description>
                        Styles and icons for new component - a2hs-guide was added. It replaced pwa-notification comppnent.
                        Push-notifications component was renamed into notification-panel.
                        --shipping modifier for notification-panel was replaced with more neutral --slim
                        Styles for a2hs-guide and notifications-panel are commented - they are optional now.
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add additional, universal class for buybox add to wishlist icon</overview>
                    <description>
                        In order to make theme compatible with magesuite-wishlist module
                        add a class to wishlist icon to allowa ajax add to wishlist badge animation
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add proper image width for autocomplete image</overview>
                    <description>
                        New image optimization functionality by default does not add additional white space in order to fit defiened image size.
                        In order to makeimage optimization faster it is recommended to define real sizes (aspect ratio) for product images.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4641</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add data-product-id to buybox wishlist icon</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add data-product-id to buybox wishlist icon in order to add selected class if given product is already added to the wishlist
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1422</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix pwa-a2hs-guide styles</overview>
                    <description>
                        Fix for: Buttons are overlapping when I added a static block
                        Fix for: Missing arrow when a static block is added (mobile)
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix translation and remove leftover custom-modal styles</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>PDP Gallery: Improved Cumulative Layout Shift</overview>
                    <description>
                        Removed styles that affect browser flow in keeping a space for image that is still loading.
                        Cleaned up webp-related code, as not supported anymore.
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>improve SEO: Add custom tag support for product details headlines, fix footer and minicart headlines, add proper styles</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>fix checkout agreements visiblity for orders with only payment step (virtual products and gift cards)</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix style of disabled swatches displayed on product tile when Back-In-Stock feature is active</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add missing styles for related products carousels in cart</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Unify "My Addresses" string to get the correct breadcrumbs translation in user area</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix amazon divider for multiple lines</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3273</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix button 'show more', which not hide after load last items</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4372</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>DEFAULT</type>
                    <overview>Bigger cleanup of the whole theme-creativeshop components, entries and folder structure</overview>
                    <description>Changes are described in breaking_changes_v18 documentation</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Implement additional function for getting video configuration so child projects can extend it</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3244</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix support for removing item from cart by setting Qty lesser than min value</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-2745</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add support for Elasticsuite Instant Search</overview>
                    <description>
                        Commit introduces changes to instant search form.mini.phtml template and provides optional components to be used
                        in projects with Elasticsuite Premium feature - Instant Search
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4665</ticket_id>
                    <doc_reference>elasticsearch_instant_search_integration.md</doc_reference>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Hide redundant bundle options wrapper for simplified bundle product (extended)</overview>
                    <description>
                        Hiding bundle options wrapper has been extended to also cover edited products that have been already placed in cart (configure simplified bundle product)
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>KRG-2352</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Allow using lazyload for background images</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Disable ATC btn. on product tile until all necessary scripts to finish the process are loaded</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAKA-1650</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add hotspots directly before and after aftersearch navigation</overview>
                    <description>
                        Additional hotspots will allow to place additional content.
                        That can be useful especially when arrangement of toolbar, sorter and filters is different on mobile and desktop layout.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-65</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>[CART] Error message appears twice</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3292</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix wrong number of steps in progress bar in checkout</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3351</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Return widget in create method of collapsible mixin</overview>
                    <description>
                        In order to fix tabs widget which is based on collapsible widget fix create method in collapsible-ext mixin
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-80</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add missing declarations for aliases</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4722</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix imports - naming issues</overview>
                    <ticket_id>P2G-1994</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix offcanvas hide method to remove old CSS class from body</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-3229</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix Daily Deal dynamic labels on tile</overview>
                    <ticket_id>DOG-1350</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Consider autoplay options in video-player, when triggering by consent status change</overview>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Compatibility with Magento 2.4.5</overview>
                    <description>
                        All the overwritten templates have been reviewed and aligned with the newest magento changes.
                        The following templates were removed due to similarity with original/not used anymore:
                            - src/Magento_Theme/templates/opengraph/cms.phtml
                            - src/Magento_Theme/templates/opengraph/category.phtml
                            - src/Magento_Theme/templates/html/defer.phtml
                            - src/Magento_Checkout/templates/cart/item/renderer/actions/move_to_wishlist.phtml
                            - src/Magento_Checkout/web/template/billing-address/details.html (almost the same as original)
                            - src/Magento_Checkout/web/template/shipping-information/address-renderer/default.html (almost the same as original)
                    </description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Prevent offcanvas navigation content from being loaded on desktop devices</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-3245</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add advanced tab to pass additional options for teaser based CC components</overview>
                    <description>
                        Additional adjustments:
                        - category image template has been overwritten and enhanced with fetchpriority attribute that can be set via view.xml
                        Changes are described in breaking_changes_v18 documentation.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>KRG-2273</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Always show edit cart link in checkout payment step</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-372</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>fix: Add condition in minicart template in order to prevent its break when getCartParam(summary_count) is not available</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-350</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix mobile nav preload for Safari browser</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-3300</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Adjust PWA guide styles for desktop</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4567</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Do not show error after click on disabled swatch with back-in-stock alert</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4747</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>[PDP] Add line break for long descriptions of attachments</overview>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1624</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix error invalid argument supplied for foreach() in included-items.phtml</overview>
                    <ticket_id>P2G-2031</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Refactor checkout next-button logic in order to make it more elastic</overview>
                    <description>Changes are described in breaking_changes_v18 documentation</description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-361</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Change user area breadcrumbs translation</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-399</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Change logic for showing/hideing popular badge</overview>
                    <ticket_id>LEDS-2301</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add DHL packstation next button mixin</overview>
                    <description>
                        In odrer to avoid going to the payment step if packstation method is checked
                        but no packstation is selected add next button validation. Also if packstation is selected
                        on next button click trigger packstation for submit
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-362</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add possibility to define accordion headline tag. Remove bottom margin, as it can be headline tag now.</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-485</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Introduce Instant Product Finder styles and scripts (for optional, private module)</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-245</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.1" date="2022-12-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Restore cart summary for tablets (override magento styles)</overview>
                    <description>HAAR-3335</description>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Remove title attribute from action links in cart (edit, remove)</overview>
                    <description>RK-484</description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.2" date="2022-12-12">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix 2 columns left layout for tablets (override magento styles)</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-3350</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.3" date="2022-12-13">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove swatches input validation from product tile</overview>
                    <ticket_id>LP-1860</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.4" date="2022-12-15">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix checkout modals when not scrollable</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4757</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.5" date="2022-12-16">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix refreshing mobile navigation after clear navigation cache</overview>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1668</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.7" date="2023-01-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add missing plugin company forms styles</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAKA-1779</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.8" date="2023-01-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add email validation to account email change in UA</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAKA-1778</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.9" date="2023-01-04">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Preselected swatch on PDP cause error with validation</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3492</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.11" date="2023-01-09">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add config in etc/view.xml that allows to show wysiwyg editor for teaser slogan and/or description in CC configurator</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add 'allow_slogan_editor' and 'allow_description_editor' configs in etc/view.xml in MageSuite_ContentConstructor/teaser paths.
                        Editors are disabled by default. When set to true `Hide/show editor` button is displayed under
                        slogan and/or description textarea in the admin panel CC configurator for teaser-based components.
                        If the feature is enabled in a child project change slogan and description wrapper tags to 'div'
                        and style nested elements (headings etc.).

                        In teaser advanced tab add a switcher to link only CTA button and not the whole slide. If links are placed inside slogan or description
                        only CTA button should be linked.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-451</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.12" date="2023-01-10">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Hide swatches and rating error message if swatch  or rating is selected</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4812</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.13" date="2023-01-18">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove "Go to" tablet link for categories that have url disabled</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-598</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.14" date="2023-01-18">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add top space for Content Constructor on PDP</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4792</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.16" date="2023-01-19">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add brand area to grid-template-areas of product tile. Align brand to left.</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4784</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add brand area to grid-template-areas of product tile. Align brand to left.</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4784</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix brand position on product tile list view</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4737</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Show configuration panel for standard bundle products</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5041</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add missing breadcrumbs in User Area</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4514</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.17" date="2023-01-18">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Clear global messages before adding product to the cart</overview>
                    <description>
                        In case when search result return single product, there is a redirect to product detail page performed on enter key.
                        After that the global message is displayed via messages. If product will be added to the cart this message will be cached
                        and displayed within the offcanvas mini cart along with the next message about product being added to the cart.
                        Similar issue can be observed when product is added to the wishlist and right after that product is added to the cart.
                        This fix clears the global messages right before fetching new messages that are going to be displayed within the offcanvas minicart.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>KRG-2436</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.18" date="2023-01-23">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Enable qty increment button when qty is equal to 1</overview>
                    <ticket_id>HAAR-3337</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.19" date="2023-01-25">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Link with disabled URL will now be a span</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-606</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.1.0" date="2023-01-31">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Adjust entries order (tabs)</overview>
                    <description>
                        Components search-result-switcher and search-result-cms are based on tabs component therefore the order of loading
                        those assets had to be adjusted to avoid style overrides with important.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>KRG-2456</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.24" date="2023-02-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add delay for input validation while editing</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add editing state for input, which is added when a user is typing. For editing state an error is hidden by CSS.
                        In order to switch off this feature set enableEditingState option to false in a child project
                        by mixin for Magento_Ui/js/form/element/abstract file.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-498</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.25" date="2023-02-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix price style for bundle items in checkout summary</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4798</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.26" date="2023-02-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Remove unnecessary space belowe in-store pickup tab in checkout</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5013</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.27" date="2023-02-03">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix update wishlist layout for simplified and standard bundles</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4770</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.28" date="2023-02-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Adjust header links styles and header user link markup</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add margin top for header link label when it's visible. Moved label outside icon wrapper in account item.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>ROT-1179</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.29" date="2023-02-08">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add visibleSlideIntersection config for teaser pagintion</overview>
                    <description>
                        visibleSlideIntersection config is a number which indicates at what percentage of
                        the slides's visibility the pagination observer's callback should be executed
                        and slide should be considered as in viewport. The default value is 0.5
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-228</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.30" date="2023-02-08">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add 'discount' classname to totals in cart</overview>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1864</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.31" date="2023-02-09">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add possibility of adding translations to extended Instant Search</overview>
                    <description>
                        Possibility of adding custom strings that will be translated was added, as it is not possible via react component itself.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-574</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.33" date="2023-02-13">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Changed PDP stylesheets order (table moved)</overview>
                    <description>
                        Moved table import to base components section so it doesn't override specific styles
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>ROT-1183</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.34" date="2023-02-16">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add optional styles, scripts and proper import in entry for MageSuite_ProductSlideGallery module</overview>
                    <ticket_id>LP-1904</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.35" date="2023-02-16">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add additional classname for offcanvas button and sorter when category has only 1 product</overview>
                    <description>
                        For categories with only 1 product "cs-toolbar__item--hide" classname has been added to offcanvas button and sorter in toolbar.
                        This will make it possible to hide these elements when needed.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1692</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.36" date="2023-02-21">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Adjust header-user-nav search-icon markup</overview>
                    <description>
                        Moved label outside icon wrapper
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>P2G-2135</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.0.37" date="2023-02-24">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add additional 'hotspot' container before toolbar to list template</overview>
                    <ticket_id>IPET-1692</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.1.0" date="2023-02-22">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Improvements for product slide gallery - add horizontal thumb nav support and reduce cls</overview>
                    <ticket_id>LP-1904</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.2.0" date="2023-02-27">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEATURE</type>
                    <overview>Add styles for Magesuite_WidgetNotificationModal module</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-625</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.2.1" date="2023-03-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Initialise tile daily deal features after minicart related products carousel is loaded</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4799</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.2.3" date="2023-03-07">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>[User Area] Move related styles from magento _module.less to scss file, to import it only in customer.ts entry</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5022</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.3.0" date="2023-03-07">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Restore script based lazyload via vanilla-lazyload with custom init.</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5019</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.3.1" date="2023-03-17">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix not working modal overlay on mobiles</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5012</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.3.2" date="2023-03-17">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>[Minicart Offcanvas carousel] Hide carousel on vertical tablet and show 2 tiles on horizonatal tablet in order to avoid too small tiles</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-5092</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.3.3" date="2023-03-16">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Minicart: disable qty-increment button, after ajax call.</overview>
                    <ticket_id>ROT-1191</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.4.0" date="2023-03-09">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Module ElasticsuiteAjaxifier style</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-654</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.4.3" date="2023-03-23">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Adjust coupon code coping classes in notification modal</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-703</ticket_id>
                </entry>
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Hide scrollbar on sliders on tablet and desktop devices</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4736</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.4.4" date="2023-03-23">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Additional classes for copy of coupon code in notification modal</overview>
                    <ticket_id>RK-703</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.4.5" date="2023-03-23">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Preload self hosted fonts to prevent CLS, FOIT and FOUT effects</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3627</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.5.0" date="2023-03-27">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Add options to custom gallery (thumbnails position)</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGS-4521</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.5.1" date="2023-03-27">
                <entry>
                    <type>FEAT</type>
                    <overview>Initialize dailydeal on tiles in carouseles rendered dynamically</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-674</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.5.2" date="2023-04-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add DD initialization in crosssell carousel in cart</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-674</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.6.0" date="2023-04-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>REFACTOR</type>
                    <overview>Refactor product teaser component basing on product tile</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-664, RK-47</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.6.1" date="2023-04-06">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add DD initialization in crosssell carousel in cart</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-674</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.6.2" date="2023-04-07">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Add DD component import to cart - checkout entries</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-674</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.6.3" date="2023-04-13">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Modify product teaser css architecture</overview>
                    <description>
                        Do not import product-tile.scss into product-tile-teaser file.
                        Product tile base styles are available as they are imported in entries.
                        Do not use product-tile variables in products-tile-teaser.scss file.
                    </description>
                    <ticket_id>RK-47</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.6.3" date="2023-04-14">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix hiding dailydeal price and badge after dailydeal expires</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-697</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.7.0" date="2023-04-19">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>First category with Image Teaser in categories nav is blocking loading the rest of categories</overview>
                    <ticket_id>NKD-3657</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.7.1" date="2023-04-19">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Extensibility fixes</overview>
                    <description>
                        Add aftersearch nav scss variable, add currentColor fill to facebook icon
                    </description>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.7.1" date="2023-08-08">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix notification modal in cart</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-824</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.7.1" date="2023-08-08">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix notification modal in cart</overview>
                    <ticket_id>TOYS-824</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
            <tag version="18.7.2" date="2023-08-010">
                <entry>
                    <type>FIX</type>
                    <overview>Fix page jumping after modal is opened</overview>
                    <ticket_id>MGP-1099</ticket_id>
                </entry>
            </tag>
        </changelog>
    </module>
</config>
